Muhammad Fadhil Musyaffa

Jakarta, Indonesia • <u>musyaffa262@gmail.com</u> • +6289670132949 • <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammad-fadhil-musyaffa/</u> • <u>https://github.com/Ader-EX</u>

Summary

Passionate Informatics student at UPN Veteran Jakarta with a passion in Frontend Development and proficiency in React, Next.js, Typescript, Tailwind CSS, MongoDB, and Prisma. demonstrating a fervent commitment to creating impactful web experiences through continuous learning and collaboration.

Education

Universitas Pembangunan Nasional Veteran Jakarta, Computer Science Bachelor of Informatics

Jakarta, Indonesia August 2021 - Present

- Cumulative GPA: 3.88/4.0
- Relevant Coursework: Web Programming, Human and Computer Interaction, Software Engineering, Object Oriented Programming, Mobile Programming, Service Oriented Software Engineering

Experiences

Indonesia's Ministry of Finance

Jakarta, Indonesia

Frontend Web Developer

February 2024 - June 2024

- Made more than 20+ authenticated pages that integrate with the backend.
- Managed a team of 4 as Frontend Lead to develop an impactful website for the Ministry of Finance, collaborating with 3 full-stack developers to ensure successful project completion.
- Successfully conducted User Acceptance Testing (UAT) to the website using a real end user with a 90%+ acceptance rate.

Peluang.co Frontend Internship

Jakarta, Indonesia November 2023 - January 2024

- Took charge of revamping and developing the Peluang.Co website, ensuring a fresh and modern design.
- Made more than 3 dynamic pages using NextJS, bringing innovation and a sleek look to the overall user experience.
- Collaborate seamlessly with the team and other developers to enhance and optimize the Peluang.Co website for maximum impact.

KSM Android UPNVJ

Jakarta, Indonesia

INJECT Member - Front-End Developer

June 2023 - November 2023

- Responsible in creating a magnificent Learning Management System website with a goal to develop student skills
- Made more than 3 dynamic pages using NextJs and other relevant frameworks, adding a layer of innovation and sophistication to the user interface.
- Collaborated with 5 Front-End Developer to develop a website using NextJS and other related web frameworks.

Leadership & Activities

KSM Android UPNVJ

Jakarta, Indonesia

Head of Communication and Information Department

January 2023 - December 2023

- Being responsible for five work programs and two non-work programs in the Communication and Information division. Responsible for managing four of the Communication and Information Department staff.
- Responsible for designing and managing the social media of KSM Android.
- Coordinated and successfully organized gathered events for 70+ people

Projects

Portfolio Website July 2024

- A Portfolio Website created to introduce myself using NextJS
- Tech Stack: NextJS, Framer Motion, Tailwind
- Link: <u>fadhil-portofolio.vercel.app</u>

Estates Rent Website March 2024

- Made a website for a real estate company that has pagination to render the datas dynamically, form to input the data, authentication. and a CRUD system.
- Tech Stack: NextJS, Typescript, KindeAuth, Supabase, and MongoDB
- Link: https://github.com/Ader-EX/Places-TS

MovieList Website November 2023

- A simple movie list website created using a free movie API
- Tech Stack: Tailwind, NextJS, ShadCN, Zod
- Github Link: https://github.com/ariefmb/fadhil-arief-finpro-web-intermediate-2023
- Website: https://layarkaca31-fadhil-arief-finpro.vercel.app

Dignition Learning Management System

June 2023 - November 2023

- A website dedicated to UPN Veteran Jakarta's student club. Dignition is a Learning Management System with a goal to develop student skills
- Tech Stack: NextJS, Tailwind, Typescript
- Link website: https://dignition.androidupnvj.com

Movie Rent App

- Movie Rent App is my final project for KSM Android's UI/UX study club. Rovie is not just a movie rental app, it's a passport to a world of immersive entertainment, designed with a passion for film and a commitment to an exceptional user experience.
- Link Prototype: https://bit.ly/PrototypeMovieRentApp
- Link Case Study: https://bit.ly/CaseStudyMovieRentApp

Certificates

Certificate of Completion - Udemy React The Complete Guide https://bit.ly/fadhil-react-udemy

November 2023

DevOps Backend di Cloud dengan GitHub - Bisa AI Academy https://bit.lv/github-bisa-fadhil

October 2023

Belajar Membuat Front-End Web untuk Pemula - Dicoding Indonesia

August 2022

https://bit.ly/dicoding-front-end

Certificate of Completion - Niagahoster UI/UX Designer https://bit.lv/rakamin-fadhil

September 2022

Skills and Interests

Technical: Git, Github, HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, NextJs, NodeJS, Golang, Tailwind, Figma,

Kotlin, Java

Language: Bahasa (Native), English (Intermediate)

Other Interests: Web Development, Algorithms and Data Structures, UI/UX Design, Mobile

Development